zelo.com 2019-04-13

# Privacy Policy - First Names and What They Mean

## Privacy Statement for Zelo.com

**We at Zelo.com **has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Zelo.com

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Logs are deleted regularly and no information is saved.

#### Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

#### Personal Information

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

**Network Advertising Initiative Statement**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ "Network Advertising Choices").

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites.  **Zelo.com  **is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   
[webmaster [at] zelo [dot] com](mailto:webmaster@zelo.com)
